Greetings to all!
Let me tell you a story
through this film.
Any locality in Chennai
could claim its dominance.
But the OG locality in Chennai
that's truly dominant
is none but Perambur.
The only place in Chennai
without a traffic signal.
It has three different types
of railway stations.
A variety of delicacies.
Paired with a variety of desserts.
It's fun all the time!
Those who hailed from Burma.
Telugu people who came from Andhra.
Anglo-Indians who immigrated from abroad.
Also, Tamil people like me who migrated
from Bengaluru.
Like this, Perambur, the land of love,
houses people
from different corners of the world.
This is a love story of my dearest friend
who has been living in this land of love
for a long time now.
And his name is...
Chirumamilla Sita Krishna!
In short... CSK!
If you would like to
learn about his character...
He's the "take it easy, life is breezy"
kind of boy.
Don't peg him as a slacker
after listening to me.
He used to be a former athlete.
Now he works a coach
"I may have not succeeded as an athlete."
"But I would love to see others succeed."
That makes him today's philanthropist,
coaching for a nominal fee.
It pains me to hype him up.
Forward and back.
Watch me.
That's it!
Hey! What are you doing?
If I had to speak about his girlfriend,
Magic...
She's an Anglo-Indian girl.
- She looks like...
- Hey!
What's with the tone?!
I can pick it up from here.
Go away!
Alright, you be the narrator.
Get lost!
He and his beehive head.
Her name is... Magic!
Living up to her name,
she's the magic in my life.
Jesus is her everything.
Her most important decisions
are made in His presence.
And she's never afraid to speak her mind.
You have to accept!
No, Father,
I don't agree with you.
Our queen loves anything black.
Including me.
They are a genuine, happy-go-lucky
Anglo-Indian family.
Magic is also a model.
It's only a matter of days
before she moves to Australia.
To adjust to Australia's timing...
she's currently working in the
Australian time zone for an IT company.
Our CSK has been in love
with Magic since college.
He has been awaiting her reply
ever since.
To this day, every New Year
and Valentine’s Day...
even during Diwali and Christmas, he greets
her with a card and diligently waits.
Stop here. Stop! Stop!
But in all these years...
He can't even enter Magic's street,
forget her heart.
You're wasting your time, bugger!
Meanwhile, when CSK's mom
had his horoscope read,
was foretold that he needs to be
married in 2 months' time.
Two months?
Yes!
If he doesn't marry now,
it might never happen.
But how?
Two months isn't enough time.
Rome wasn't built in a day.
However, our CSK aims to achieve it
within 2 months.
Let's wait and watch what unfolds.
Dad, I just wrapped up training.
- Meet at Shalimar as usual?
- Yes!
- You coming?
- On my way
Okay.
- Let’s go, guys!
- Sure, let's go.
Uncle, what is all this?
Just for fun!
What are you having?
Mom has already made us breakfast.
Don’t be a Mama’s boy!
Bro!
Yes, Sir.
For me, two sets of Appam and Paya.
What, Paya, Sir?
Pepper Paya!
Guys, give him your orders.
Parotta, egg kurma.
One egg dosa.
I'll have the same.
Great song!
Bhaskar!
Hey! What?
Haven't you seen girls before?
Quit bothering them!
Who do you think you are?
- Get lost!
- You don't know these people.
It's 'cause of them Anglo-Indian women
are not able to roam freely.
Delinquents!
- Hey! Who's the delinquent?
- Dirtbag!
Who are you calling a dirt bag?
Hey, Bhaskar!
Don't do it!
- I’ll knock your teeth out!
- Dad, cut it out!
Don't you dare! I'm warning you!
Zip it!
Do you expect me to sit
and take insults?
- I didn't say anything wrong.
- Just pipe down!
Dad, why did you climb over
the table just now?
Hey, Bhaskar!
We thought you didn't like Anglo-Indians?
What do you mean?
Your order, sir.
- Why is Anglo-Indian a big deal?
- Exactly!
Family first gawks,
then tries to cover it up.
I wasn't gawking at them, Uncle.
I was checking who it was.
You were drooling over them.
We saw you gawking.
Do you really think
we have a chance with them?
Hey! Who's "we"?
My son's a stud!
What does he lack?
He doesn't lack anything.
They're not the kind to be wooed easily.
Half of them are foreigners.
Your son should find a girl
in some village in Andhra instead.
He has better chances out there.
Hey! Shut up!
You guys are going overboard!
I'm challenging you all.
Right here in Perambur,
if my son, Chirumamilla Sita Krishna,
fails to marry an Anglo-Indian girl.
My name is no longer
Chirumamilla Aadhinarayana Bhaskar.
Let's go, my boy!
You spoke fiercely!
No, that's too far away.
We'll ride straight.
Damn you, man!
Remember to wear this.
Hey, Bhaskar!
I was saying to you
that you spoke out of rage.
Hey!
I didn't speak out of rage.
I’ve been feuding
with some Anglo-Indians for a while.
That's why I was enraged
to hear them speak that way.
Why can't you fall in love
with Anglo-Indian girls?
Listen, they're very beautiful.
Dad, please be practical.
Even the local girl
doesn't give me a second look.
And you want me to aim
for Anglo-Indians.
Take it I find one girl...
Mom would never approve.
Really?!
It sounds like
you have something going on.
Dad, as if I'm that lucky.
Listen, Dad.
All I can do
is marry whoever Mom picks out.
Even if I were to have a love marriage...
it would be with Mom’s approval
and a girl from our own caste.
Hey!
What now?
Aren't you ashamed?
I lost my love
because of caste discrimination.
No matter whom you love,
I'll support you all the way.
Mummy?
Your Mother has no control over me.
Hand that over!
Give it to me
If you're wondering
why he’s staring him down...
it's because CSK's mother
is a fierce character.
Vakkalanka Sarala!
She's the head of this family,
and everything needs to be.
She runs a flour shop.
Even when her sons
and husband make their living
She proudly refuses
to borrow a dime from them.
How did you forget
to bring loose change?
She's a Woman of Steel!
Nothing happens in their family
without her approval.
She's extremely devout!
What kind of dress is this?
Girls who wear sleeveless
won't be suitable for my family.
For her, everything is religion and caste.
It applies not only to her family...
She is a key member of her community.
Meet CSK's brother.
Chirumamilla Chiranjeevi Shankar.
State government employee!
What is this?
Why didn’t you check this?
He lives up to his mom's expectations.
Look at him.
Learn from your younger brother.
How do you refer to yourself
as Chiranjeevi's brother?
Shame on you! Kneel down!
Even after being Chiranjeevi's brother...
is this the most you could score?
Is Chiranjeevi's brother
working in an athlete camp?
Couldn't you find a better job?
Whatever!
If there is someone
he loves in this house...
It has to be his sister,
Chirumamilla Sathyavadhi,
and her daughter, Bommi.
- Out!
- Dad!
Who is it? Who's it?
Dad, it's time!
This is Chirumamilla Aadhinarayana Bhaskar.
Even his name is as long as a train.
Which is why he works
at the train manufacturing unit.
I can still see a white patch.
Do it right!
His friends matter most to him.
Even at his age...
He cycles between tea shops
and Shalimar with them.
Starts each morning with a football match.
Cause he's from the sports reservation.
Our daddy here is a total playboy.
You haven't seen it all.
He does one thing
that Mummy can't forgive him for.
Hey, why are you taking mine?
At dusk, he drowns in alcohol.
- Hey, Boomer!
- Dad!
But when he's sober,
he's nothing less than a scared cat.
Don't say anything!
Hey!
Coming, dear.
How many times should I call you?
Don't you have any responsibility?
Uncle is waiting with wedding invites.
I was stuck in a meeting
Are they waiting?
Get inside. Go!
Brother!
Welcome!
I'll bring the coffee.
- How have you been?
- Real good, Bhaskar.
- Look at him all grown up.
- Welcome!
Looks like
you're still practicing football.
It got me a job in the railway.
How can I leave that behind?
That's not the case, Uncle.
He still considers himself a child.
Always hanging out with friends.
He's a fun character, dear.
Please hand out the invitation.
Make sure you bring your family, Bhaskar.
- Okay, dear?
- For sure!
Please sit.
The wedding is during the weekend.
- No excuses. You must come.
- Of course, I won't miss it.
Isn't the girl form our caste?
It's a love marriage.
What do you expect us to do?
So what?
Do you agree to anything?
Our caste deserves some respect.
Sarala, that's enough.
Sarala...
kids these days don’t listen to us anymore.
- Sathyavadhi!
- Mom!
Mom?
Who chose your husband?
It was you, Mother.
Chiranjeevi!
Mom?
Which caste will you marry into?
A girl from our caste, as per your choice.
Krishna!
Mom!
Who will you marry?
- Krishna!
- Mom!
Whoever you choose.
Did you see?
Say it the right way,
and everyone will listen.
It all depends on upbringing.
Alright, our upbringing wasn’t right.
We'll have another kid
and raise it properly.
For now, just come to this wedding.
When is it?
25th of next month.
My husband and Chiranjeevi can't take off.
We can’t make it!
Oh!
I see how it is.
The other two boys are yet to be married.
We'll see!
Hey, come on!
I'll see you around.
We'll see, he says!
Sarala, this isn't right.
I've arranged so many marriages
in our community…
and now one person
from our own family marries an outsider
do you expect me
to bless that marriage?
If anyone attends that wedding...
that’s the end of it!
Phew!
Seeing what my mom did
scared even me.
If I told them about Magic
they'll bury me alive.
You just have to say it the right way.
Hey, no matter how he says it,
his mother will never agree.
And if he waits for her approval,
he’ll never get married.
Hey, Big guy. So what?
Do you expect me to elope with her?
- I would love to see you elope.
- Damn you!
Maggie, what do you say?
Aren't you guys in love?
Who needs permission?
- Just run away together!
- Bro!
Like that's ever going to happen.
Are you implying
that I don't have the guts?
Bro! You have the guts.
But the girl has to agree to it.
It's delusional to talk about marriage
when it's an unrequited love.
I don't get it!
Hey! Shut up!
She likes me a lot.
Liking someone and being in love
are not the same.
What else?
That girl hasn't invited him
over to her house once.
She doesn't even let him onto her street.
Her relatives don’t even know
that he exists.
And he calls this love!
Shameless!
Hey, I'll end you--
Hey, it's Magic!
Hello, Magic!
Hey Krishna, where are you at?
Here, with my friends.
You know my church, right?
I guess so.
Can you get there, man?
I want you to meet my uncle.
I was just telling him about you.
You spoke to your Uncle...
about me!
Yeah, man
Okay, okay.
I'm on my way.
Dude, hear me out.
I know everything about Anglos-Indians.
They are everywhere in Bangalore.
Really?
I'm telling the truth.
Their women are very smart.
Unless a guy is serious...
they don't let him anywhere
near their community.
Then why would she want me to
meet her Uncle?
It means that she's serious about you.
Go there and fix a date for the marriage.
Really?!
Trust me, dude!
I know everything about Anglo-Indians.
Oh, wow! Beautiful girls!
- Oh, no!
- Hey!
I slipped, Dude!
Dude, she’s coming to us.
- Hi
- Hi!
- Hi, Krishna.
- Hi, Magic.
Thanks for coming here, man.
- You must have been busy?
- No problem!
Not even close.
He was waiting by his phone
for your call.
Hey, Bugger. Really?
He's just mocking me!
You have to meet my Uncle, okay?
Uncle, please come here.
Uncle?
This is the man they were talking about.
We can even have the wedding here, right?
It'll be awesome!
- Hello, gentlemen!
- Hi, Uncle!
I'm Rosario.
You're Krishna, right?
You even know his name?
How could I not?
Magic has spoken so much about Krishna.
Dude...
You believe me now?
I know everything about Anglo-Indians.
Keep it down.
What is your friend saying?
Nothing, Uncle. Chill!
It must be because of this sudden meet-up.
That must be it!
You're absolutely right
Magic will not do anything
without a reason.
And if she chooses, she chooses right!
See if everything checks out?
Uncle, that’s all he’s done so far.
Shut up.
It might be some formality.
Looks good to me, Uncle!
Why are you looking there?
Look here.
He is down here.
Him?
Yeah, he's the one I suggested.
I heard you run an athletic camp
in this area?
And he happens to be interested
in athletics.
See if he fits the bill.
Okay, he can join my classes.
You happy, child?
That's it?
Isn't there anything else?
Like what?
What else do you want, bugger?
I'll drop him off tomorrow myself.
Okay?
See you. Bye.
- Yeah, bye.
- Bye!
- See you!
- Come, let's go child!
- She's gone.
- Are you happy?
Dude, don't get upset.
If she shared this much with her uncle,
it must be love.
Trust me, dude.
I know everything about Anglo-Indians.
I’ll kill you!
You’re done for!
Keep walking!
What are you waiting for?
♪ Keeping the Lord in my thoughts ♪
I kept on walking
Is it?
God, try to stop me if you can,
I’m going in with full frustration
♪ Keeping the Lord in my thoughts ♪
♪ I kept on Walking ♪
♪ God, try to stop me if you can, ♪
♪ I’m going in with full frustration ♪
♪ Oh, my love, Diana ♪
♪ You’re the one I love ♪
♪ If you and I become one ♪
♪ We’ll be lovestruck couples! ♪
♪ I became a total fool because of you ♪
♪ Became a hit and got hurt too ♪
♪ If you touch me, I become fit ♪
♪ But bro,
There’s no “touching” happening here ♪
♪ Sharp girl, Sharp girl ♪
♪ The boy asking for a pair is a dummy ♪
Who’s it for?
Grab a plate.
Hey!
Get lost!
♪ The boy asking for a pair is a dummy ♪
♪ After falling, head over heels,
I’ve turned into a fiery force ♪
You look great in that dress.
- It makes you look like a model.
- Really?
Dude, what’s with him?
Hey, Baba, let's go have some tea.
Your tea addiction
is what gives corporations power.
Consume organic instead.
Did you forget about
your girl in Bangalore?
Stop flirting with every girl you see.
Do you want me to call your girlfriend?
Let’s go to the tea shop.
I'm already in enough trouble.
♪ In your presence,
I lose myself ♪
♪ I've been caught
In love's relentless pull ♪
♪ A flame I shouldn't lay a finger on ♪
♪ Instead of finding love,
I find myself conquered by it ♪
♪ Sharp girl, Sharp girl ♪
♪ The boy asking for a pair is a dummy ♪
♪ After falling, head over heels,
I’ve turned into a fiery force ♪
♪ Sharp girl, Sharp girl ♪
♪ The boy asking for a pair is a dummy ♪
♪ After falling, head over heels,
I’ve turned into a fiery force ♪
What's your next move?
I'm going to have another dosa.
Uncle, he wants to know your plan in life.
Even the kid gets it, but you don't.
- What does he lack?
- Thanks, Mom.
He's a coach.
And earns a good living.
What more does he need?
Look here...
making a living by any means is not life.
Dad is a central government employee.
I work for the state government.
Unless he finds a good government job,
he will find a good girl to marry.
Okay, boomer!
That's enough, Brother!
Studying and working
aren't what life is about either.
It doesn't give you any right
over others.
Everyone has their own version of winning.
Hey, Chiranjeevi!
Stop wasting your time with him.
Let him keep running
in the streets.
When you marry a good girl...
- Then he'll feel jealous.
- Yeah, right!
Sure thing!
I've heard it all before.
It's all a lie, my son!
Every word is a lie!
No matter how successful you become...
you'll only marry a girl you don't like.
Just like I married your mother.
Good lord!
Every day is the same with you.
You're drunk!
Shut up. Don't talk.
The girl I loved
was from a different caste.
So, my Dad got me married to you.
Dad!
It was a loveless marriage.
Sure!
Then explain
how I got pregnant in a month.
That's personal... my weakness
Let's not go there.
The man behind closed doors
isn't the same man outside.
- Right?
- What do you want now?
- What do I want?!
- I ought to!
I want peace!
I want to be rid of you all.
Freedom!
I want freedom!
Can you give me that?
- He's getting out of hand.
- Hey, I won't spare you, people.
Are you going to sleep or not?
Oh, my Shanthi!
My dear, Shanthi!
Always calling her name
instead of mine.
I do all the work,
but she gets the credit.
Don't take it out
while I'm still talking.
I can't hear a thing.
I won't be able to anymore.
Feel free to say anything you want.
Your hair is such a mess to deal with.
- Yay! Daddy! daddy!
- Sweetie!
Welcome, Son-in-law.
Greet him!
You look happy.
Does that mean you won't come back home?
Nothing like that, Son.
She's miserable here without you.
Then why doesn’t she come back home?
Your mom will be there too, right?
What did she do to you?
- Not me, but my daughter--
- Hey!
She calls her a nutcase.
Sathya?
I keep trying to explain...
What mild autism is?
If she were fully autistic,
she might have killed her.
How's it my fault
if she doesn't understand?
I'm still fond of my kid.
It's the only reason I still speak to you.
I am asking you to live as a family
away from your folks.
If you're not on board...
I'd rather stay here at my mothers
for my kid.
Hey!
What are you talking about?
Life is all about compromises.
I searched our whole community
to find you a respectable family.
He's a great husband!
Did you think I will feed you forever?
It's okay if you don't feed me.
I can live on my own.
I'll raise her alone.
No one can enslave an educated woman.
Next, to this side.
Krishna?
- Hi!
- Hey, Bugger!
He's all yours!
Huh?
She says he's your responsibility
from now on.
Can’t you even understand that?
Useless!
I never said I didn't get it.
I just didn't hear it.
Soon to judge!
- Hey, child. Say hi to your coach.
- Hi, Coach!
Hi, come here!
What's your full name?
Alexander Arnold.
Alexander Arnold...
Whatever!
Follow those kids and start running.
- Run! Run! Run!
- Yes, coach.
Hey, Bugger, thank you.
- We'll wait there. Come on.
- Please carry on.
- Bye.
- Get lost!
Everyone, start stretching!
You're looking at him as if you’ve
just met him for the first time.
Crazy bugger!
He hasn’t changed a bit since college.
♪ She's as dazzling as a glass marble ♪
♪ Your silent gaze overwhelms me ♪
♪ She's dazzling enough to slay ♪
♪ I'm swept by strange feelings ♪
♪ There's barely time for a hello ♪
- Nice glasses!
- It's a fake.
I just wear it for style.
♪ My whole world is changing ♪
- Hang on a minute.
- Hi!
I’ve always wanted to explore street food.
Can you take me?
You see...
I'll pay for it.
Fine, let's go!
Cheap skate!
Come!
♪ Walking with you,
I wish the road would never end ♪
♪ I'm not myself anymore...
Enough, enough ♪
♪ At that quiet moment,
I'll stand by you, hand in hand ♪
♪ Will this moment last a little longer? ♪
♪ I pleaded with tears in my eyes ♪
Wow!
♪ Will this moment last a little longer? ♪
♪ I pleaded with tears in my eyes ♪
Amazing!
It's like a wonderland.
Hey!
Wonderland?
- That's a good name for it.
- Yeah!
Hey, Bugger!
What was so important
that you had to tell me?
Tomorrow, we have to perform
a skit at college.
That too, in English.
You're well aware of my English.
I had it written in Tamil.
Can you please translate it into English?
Is that all?
Is this what you call important?
That's it
What else?
Fine, tell me.
My love!
In this fast-paced world...
the only face
that brings me peace is yours.
Even though my mind is filled
with thousands of thoughts...
Your name is the only one among them.
This is not just love.
It's a promise.
This is not just a moment's feeling...
It's a lifetime decision!
Magic...
I love you!
- Me too--
- This is a dialogue from my skit.
Oh, okay, okay.
Were you about to say something?
I interrupted!
Nothing! I'm leaving!
Wait! Magic? Magic!
Magic!
Some power held him back that day
from proposing his love to me.
So far, I respect that power.
I believe Jesus is guiding me.
I have a doubt.
Millions of people worship Him.
Everyone shares their trouble.
But ignoring it all...
He’s getting in the way of you two.
Some nerve, I say.
Are you mocking me?
What do you think?
If you like the guy,
just marry him already.
Instead,
My liking him alone doesn't matter.
Our family matters too!
Moreover...
I like him. That's about it.
There's a world of difference
between liking someone and loving them.
Let's see!
I'd say they're closer than you think.
What happened, Dad?
It's about Barbara.
What happened to her?
What do you think?!
She's pregnant now!
How many times did I warn you?
To be careful
with these bloody Tamil buggers.
She never bloody listens to me.
Hold your horses, Davey!
This is our daughter.
No use in yelling.
Magic, take your cousin inside.
Yeah, sure.
Contact a family doctor.
Let's abort it!
Don't be stupid, man.
See, Dave
Listen...
Let's talk to the Tamil guy first.
Let's see where his family stands
on this matter.
You can certainly speak
with the Tamil guy's family.
Say what?
You want me to talk to those folks?
It's embarrassing to even admit.
The grand daughter of Randy Wilkins
is marrying a Tamil--
What man!
You're being stupid!
Dave, you were born
and raised here after all.
Where did all this pride come from?
What?
Is this a joke to you?
Then what, man?
More than your family and pride...
your daughter's happiness
is most important.
Listen, Dave,
her happiness is most important.
He was never going to
tell his folks about us.
Cheater!
Our boys are best!
After getting married...
we should just move to
Australia or England and settle down.
We have no future in this place.
Magic, I only have one thing to say to you.
Don't fall for these Tamil guys.
Bum Buggers!
Big sis!
My daughter just graduated college.
Since she wishes to continue
her studies in Chennai.
So we came for admission.
- Graduated, huh?
- Yeah!
Brother! Brother!
Where are you off to?
Get over here!
Give her your blessing.
What’s all this for?
Best of luck, dear!
We wish you all the best.
Please sit.
Brother-in-law!
She's a topper!
Is that so?
Very good! Very good!
Even the principal
wrote her a letter of appreciation.
Impressive!
Quick! Quick!
- Oh, no!
- What's wrong?
I can't read Telugu.
It slipped my mind. Hand it to me.
You read it out.
That won't be necessary.
Krishna needs to get married
in two months.
Let’s get them married first,
she can study later.
She can attend the college
from here, too.
No problem!
I had the same idea, Big sis.
Tanisha would like the same.
- Is that right?
- I had the same thought, Auntie.
The man of the hour is here!
Couldn’t have picked a worse timing.
Big sis, so is this official?
Hey! Whatever I say goes!
I don't go back on my word.
Your daughter is for Krishna.
That's enough, sis.
We can have the wedding next month.
Sure thing!
I'll fix the engagement date soon.
You're fine with it, right?
Ye-- Yes, Mom!
Super!
There you go!
- What do you say?
- Super.
What about you?
What did you say to me?
That I can go anywhere
from Madras to Mumbai.
But your love for me remains steady.
And now you want to marry
Lawrence Thangaraj.
While you're there...
How do you expect me
to overcome my needs?
Oh!
Now you care about your needs?
But when I tried to make a move on you...
didn’t you say you were
saving yourself for marriage.
So, you'd never make a move.
You're useless!
Hang up!
Don't hang up! Don't--
Damn, that woman!
- Right! Smash it on your head.
- Hey, Baba!
Are you nuts?
What are you doing?
Hey, morons!
How could you not stop him from
smashing the bottle against his head?
You just got here
and don't run your mouth.
For the past two hours,
he spoke about everything he wanted to.
It's his third time around.
That too after having half a beer.
- What is all this?
- She threw me away!
My love is doomed!
Five years down the drain.
I'm at the brink of getting drunk myself.
Did your girl leave you too?
She has to love him first
before she can leave him.
It's unrequited love, Dude.
Five years of love!
It's all gone now.
Hey, Bangalore!
If you call it unrequited love again...
I'll crack your head open with this bottle.
Pissing me off!
I’m being forced to marry my cousin.
That’s good news!
Please marry her!
Either way, you won't propose to Magic.
Why do you guys do this to me?
I can neither get the approval
of my mother
nor can I confess my love to the girl
so, as my last resort,
I came to my friends to vent out...
but all you guys do is mock me.
You can’t even empathize
with your friend.
Are you even good friends?
Hey!
What do you want from us?
You proposed to her
during your days in college...
and still moping around for her reply.
I’ll smack you!
Call her right away
and find out whether she loves you.
Enough with the crocodile tears.
You have a point!
- I'm calling her right now.
- Do it!
What’s up, Krishna?
Magic!
I want to talk to you
about something important.
What about?
It's about our love.
Look, Krishna, talk about anything else.
Don’t ever call me about love.
You irritating Bugger!
Magic--
"Bugger."
Shall I call Magic again?
Dude, check out the time.
It's 02:30 a.m.
Just go to sleep!
She works in an Australian shift.
She would have just left for work.
If I don’t act now...
I'll end up marrying my cousin.
This will be last attempt with Magic.
If it doesn't work,
I'll marry my cousin.
So as soon as you drop me off,
I'm going to call her.
Are you not ashamed of yourself?
You still want to call her
after all the humiliation.
A man should be the dominant one.
Right!
I'm a man, and I should be dominant.
- I won't call her again.
- Don't!
Never in my life!
Stop it! Stop it!
What happened?
What are you doing?
I'm calling Magic.
For God’s sake!
Shameless fellow!
Love leaves no space for shame.
Hey, bugger! What do you want?
Call me whatever you prefer...
but don't ever call me Bugger!
Oh, God!
What do you want, Krishna?
Am I not allowed to speak anymore?
Look here, Krishna.
You can talk anything apart from love.
We're still good friends.
Of course!
All these years,
I've loved only you and waited for you.
I deserve it!
This is how you'd treat me.
Because you take boys for granted.
Hello! Slow down!
Why should I?
You can't just drive recklessly
because there's no traffic.
Oh, not me!
You'd better be afraid of me.
Afraid?
Afraid of what?
Afraid of...?
You're just afraid of
falling in love with me.
Are you guys still using
these corny dialogues?
- So funny!
- Sure!
We are funny!
It must be so funny
to have someone love you this much.
It must be funny watching us suffer.
Until my final breath--
Hey, don't you have any sense?
Can't you hear me?
Don't you comprehend anything?
I'm being patient with you.
If you keep this up,
I'll file a complaint.
Magic, I didn't mean to.
The car shouldn't go over
40 Miles per hour.
He's simply bloody irritating.
Not me again.
Tell me!
Look, Magic...
I have no ounce of self-respect.
It’s impossible to humiliate me.
Even in sudden death...
I'll love you!
Hello?
- My head is injured.
- Hello, Magic?
[over phone]
See what happened out there.
Check what happened to Madam.
Hello? Hello?
- She's bleeding!
- Bleeding?
Hey, help me move.
Take them to hospital.
Be careful!
She was on a call.
Where's her phone?
Someone pick up the phone.
There it is!
Please pick up the phone.
Hello!
- It hurts!
- It's alright
How did it happen?
Rash driving!
Did you tell him to slow down?
I kept repeating it.
What about the security?
Sir, you're needed out here.
I'll be right back.
Okay, okay, please don't cry.
Hey!
You caused this!
You proposed your love,
and I met with an accident.
Didn’t I tell you we weren’t meant to be?
Yeah, you did!
Now look here.
My favorite T-shirt is covered in blood.
Relax!
How did this happen?
Magic...
Sir, he applied sudden brake...
and it caused me
to bump into the front seat.
Sir, can't you come at a better time?
Do you have to inquire right away?
You can file the report later.
Can't you see she's in pain?
Isn't she your colleague?
Can't you wait until she returns to work?
Leave and mind you business.
So, am I not allowed
to treat my patients?
Wait, what?
Oh, no, he is a Doctor!
- Sorry! Sorry!
- Can’t you get anything right?
Sorry, Magic!
I swear
I didn't know he was a Doctor.
- I can barely lift my hand.
- Doctor!
Sir! Sir!
Sir!
- Sorry about that.
- What now?
I didn’t know you were a doctor.
I'm sorry.
Please come back.
Please, Sir.
Magic.
Nurse, tend to her wounds
and bandage them.
Okay, Doctor.
- Get her to an X-ray.
- Yes, sir.
Now, where is that X-ray?
I was the driver.
Weren’t you the punk at Shalimar
the other day?
You don't know how to drive.
But aspire to fly it.
What happened?
Watch where you’re going!
Nurse, is she feeling better?
Nothing to worry about.
She’s been given six stitches.
You can see your sister now.
Sister?
Do we look like siblings to you?
Get lost!
Magic?
You're alright. We can leave.
Magic?!
- I’ll call you back
- Are you okay?
Baby girl, what happened?
- I'm fine!
This is Krishna.
My best friend!
He came at the right time
and helped me.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, man
I really appreciate it.
I'll take her from here and go home.
Thanks again!
Dude, go bring the car.
Go quickly!
Careful
- Let's go.
- Take it slow.
Mom, Dad.
Just give me two minutes, okay?
I'll be there.
- Just two minutes
- Okay
Come on, let's go.
She’s talking personally.
Leave her.
That’s her business.
Sorry, Krishna.
I said many things out of pain.
It's okay, Magic.
Take care of your health.
Yeah, sure!
- See you later.
- Bye.
Hey, Bugger.
Hey, careful!
Here's your report.
Thanks.
♪ Don't drift away... ♪
♪ A bloom whose eyes
Leave hearts enchanted ♪
♪ You bloom with honeyed sweetness ♪
♪ Don't drift away ♪
♪ A bewitching flame of longing ♪
♪ So gently, ♪
♪ You set my heart ablaze ♪
♪ And stole it away ♪
♪ You turn back just once ♪
♪ Yet that single glance
Haunts me for countless moments ♪
♪ In an instant ♪
♪ My heart melts. ♪
♪ Standing close to me ♪
♪ Your quiet whispers a thousand lessons ♪
♪ Like rain sinking into thirsty sand ♪
♪ You slip into every part of me,
Again and again. ♪
♪ In the endless sky, ♪
♪ Two clouds reunite ♪
♪ Across every distance ♪
♪ My loneliness travels to find its end ♪
♪ Like a dream ♪
♪ We weave stories
Until they blossom into love ♪
♪ Deep within my soul ♪
♪ Desire quietly overflows. ♪
♪ A single enduring glance
From you is enough ♪
♪ Glancing ♪
♪ All I seek is
A few more moments with you ♪
♪ Longing... ♪
♪ In the endless sky ♪
♪ Two clouds reunite ♪
♪ Across every distance ♪
♪ My loneliness travels to find its end ♪
♪ Like a dream ♪
♪ We weave stories
Until they blossom into love ♪
♪ Deep within my soul ♪
♪ Desire quietly overflows ♪
♪ A single enduring glance
From you is enough ♪
♪ Glancing ♪
♪ All I seek is
A few more moments with you ♪
♪ Longing ♪
Sathya, What's taking so long?
- Almost done.
- Hurry up!
All of you take a bath.
Will do!
Oh no, rice!
I don't want to eat rice.
Mom, I want some bread omelet.
You're going to get smacked.
For one more month,
no egg or non-veg.
What?!
Until the Purattasi month is over.
What's all this?
- Go over to your Uncle.
- Come to me.
Sit.
I'll take you outside
and buy whatever you want to eat.
Hey!
If I find out
that you had meat outside.
I won't let you back in the house.
Especially, you!
I wouldn’t dream of it.
Dad! What’s happening?
Never mind her.
We are heading to Shalimar right after.
And feast on four appams and paya.
Paya?
Pepper Paya!
- My little brother.
- What?
Do you know why Mom's fasting?
Why's that?
For you and Chiranjeevi to marry the girl
you've always dreamed of.
Girl of your dreams.
Magic. Magic.
Dad, I am going to be fasting.
Don't spoil me!
- Bloody, old man.
- What's with him?
He might be more shameless than I am.
Dude?
Whenever your girl asks to come home,
would you take me along?
What nonsense are you talking about?
You see, your girl called you over...
It might lead to something steamy.
So, I feel I might get in the way.
Dude, am I right?
It's the first time she's invited me over.
I thought it'd feel less awkward
with you there.
But you're talking nonsense.
If a girl calls someone over,
it doesn't mean she's calling for that.
Lust may be part of a man's life,
but it cannot define it.
You don't have to tag along.
Get off the bike.
- Get off!
- Sorry, dude!
I was out of line.
Please go!
If you say anything else,
I'll kill you.
Magic?
Woah!
What a beauty?
- Hey!
- I meant the house, Dude.
- Hi, Krishna. Hi!
- Hi.
- Please come in.
- Coming! Coming!
All these plants inside the house
remind me of Bangalore.
Hey, Dad!
They're here!
Hey, Krishna!
Hi! Hi! Welcome home!
Come! Come!
- Who’s this?
- Greetings, Uncle.
He's my friend, Uncle.
Baba! Bangalore Baba!
Hey, Bangalore!
Nice, Man!
Welcome, have a seat.
Have a seat. Sit down.
Sir, I know all about Anglo-Indians.
All friends in my area know me.
Hey, Baba, I'm part white,
yet I speak good Tamil.
Why are you struggling to speak English?
You deserved that.
- Dad.
- Yeah, Baby girl.
Fix them a drink.
Yeah, done, sure.
So, boys,
what would you like to have?
- Tea, coffee--
- Whisky or Brandy?
Sir, is this for real?
Hey, this is our custom, man.
Fine, what do you like to drink?
Then I’ll have a whisky on the rocks.
Not bad, man!
Krishna, what are you having?
- I'll--
- Sir!
He doesn't drink any liquor.
He's a good boy!
Does that make us bad people!
That's some backwards logic.
No, sir.
I only said what people usually say.
Drinking is a personal choice, Baba!
No one has the right to judge them.
Moderation is the key.
Correct, sir!
Drinking at home should be normalized.
You're rocking, Sir.
Now you're catching up.
Alright.
One whiskey on the rocks!
Dude, he wasn't kidding around.
What's with them?
They have drinks at home.
Have fun, Dude!
Baba, I’ve poured you one small.
Finish this and I’ll refill it.
Krishna, I’ll keep this here.
- Drink whenever you feel like it.
- Uncle, I don't want it.
Hey, it's just wine, Krishna.
It doesn't matter. I don't want it.
Krishna!
You’re insulting us.
Dad, leave him be.
No, no.
I'll drink it for Uncle.
Yeah!
That’s my boy
Alright!
I, too, shall fix a drink for myself.
Wine is straight fire, Sir.
Was it homemade?
Yes, homemade.
I even sell it if you want to buy.
- So it was a sample.
- You said it best.
Hey, bugger.
Dad always jokes around.
Don't mind, okay.
Come, let's eat.
Come on!
Make yourselves comfortable.
There were so many surprises
with the drinks.
I don't even know what to expect in food.
Nothing special.
Beef fry, beef biryani, chilly beef.
Pork fry, and meat.
That's all!
Pass me the pork.
I'll serve Krishna.
You're going to get smacked!
For one more month,
no egg or non-veg.
Until the Purattasi month is over.
Try Aunty’s Pork.
Her cooking is special.
- Just try.
- Do you want some beef?
That's enough for me.
[offering prayers]
Eat your fill. Don't feel shy.
That's enough.
Dude, stop!
Just hold on a second, Dude.
Beef looked fire!
You ruined my chances of a good feast.
What the hell is your problem?
Dude...
If Magic and I got together
How will I tell my mother
that they cook beef and pork?
That too, during Puratasi month.
Dude, you mustn't be thinking
from this angle.
You have to convince Magic
to adjust to your family's liking.
Because you’re going to live
with your parents.
First, ask her what Puratasi even means.
You keep thinking like your Mom.
Magic, I'm sorry.
On that day, my mother warned me strictly
not to eat non-veg because it's Puratasi.
So I was afraid
that I might end up eating.
Hey, bugger!
I understand!
But it was no way to behave
in front of my parents.
- It was humiliating!
- Oh, no, I'm sorry, Magic.
I'm really sorry, Magic.
Okay, forget it.
Do you know what Puratasi is?
And why don't we eat meat?
Yes, I know all about Puratasi.
- Is it?
- The most peaceful time for our people.
Peaceful? How's that?
Yes, most of you avoid eating non-veg.
So we can get chicken and fish cheaply.
Apart from that,
why would I care about Puratasi?
What?
Come along!
Hello.
Yes, sir.
Are you at our camp?
- I'll be there in 10 minutes.
- Hey, there!
Hey, what are you doing here?
I told you about the check-up.
Oh, right!
Listen, she's my niece.
I brought her to the hospital.
Suddenly, a parent has arrived
at the camp to pay the fee.
- Can you babysit her for 10 Minutes?
- Yeah, sure!
- What's your name?
- Bommi!
That’s a cool name!
Who named you?
My dad, who else.
Okay, what's your name?
My name is...
Magic!
Oh! You're that Magic?
Do you know me?
Yes, I know you very well.
I've heard about you often.
About me? From whom?
Who else? My Uncle.
Magic is like this and that...
I like her this much.
He's been saying it for a long time.
Don't you like my uncle?
Your Uncle--
Let's go.
I think I like someone
Who?
Clifton?
Then?
Krishna.
- Who?
- CSK.
CSK?!
What? Are you mad?
I told you not to fall
for these Tamil guys.
Did you learn nothing
from my experience?
Don’t stereotype, Barbara.
Just because your man did it
doesn't mean they're all the same.
Aren't many of our folks happy
marrying them?
No way, Dude.
We can't live happily.
It'll be very tough.
Why dude?
You want to know why?
Mom already made up her mind
about my cousin.
If I decided to marry Magic instead...
no one else in the family
can be happy.
What do I care if others are happy or not?
Isn't our happiness enough?
Love is all about the couple.
Not family.
The couple are the problem.
The problem in loving the boys here is...
the way they see us.
Anglo means easily approachable.
All they care about is sex.
Once the serious commitment comes up...
it runs into danger.
Dress appropriately.
Don't party too much.
They don't know our culture and torture us.
Look at Clifton following you
everywhere with his eyes.
Ask him out.
You'll live a good life.
What do you want me to do?
Do I really have to choose between them?
Choosing is your only way out, Dude!
That too, within a month.
You have to convince
both Magic and your mother.
Within 30 days.
30 Days is too much.
15 days at most.
It's all up to Magic.
It’s quite a conundrum.
What do I do now?
Let me tell you what to do.
Test him.
What?
Give him a test.
Test the waters
to see if it works out.
What if it doesn’t work out?
If he doesn't fit in?
If he doesn’t work out,
don’t even bring it up at home.
Keep it quiet!
If it works out, then take the risk.
Alright, let me give it a shot.
Okay. I'll give it a shot.
Hey, Dude, move it!
Up your game, Dude.
Oh, no!
There it goes!
♪ I'm trapped beyond escape ♪
♪ Everything keeps piling up ♪
♪ Every nerve tingles ♪
♪ I've been hit hard by love ♪
♪ Hey, idiot! ♪
♪ Damn, you fool ♪
♪ You're trapped Damn, you fool ♪
♪ I'm trapped beyond escape ♪
I saw her in a party dress
for the first time.
What kind of clothing is that?
Hey, Dude!
Anglos' always dress to kill.
I knew that already.
All this time, it felt like
only I was checking her out.
But now when I think about
marrying her...
I feel everyone around is checking her out.
♪ She's got me chasing after her ♪
Like that!
She hugs everyone head-on.
- Why can't she hug them sideways?
- Dude!
It’s infuriating to watch these things.
It’s very wrong, Bro.
Hey, Bugger!
How about we try a different approach?
Meaning?
Like a situationship.
Or a fling.
Living together.
Something like that.
Situationship just means...
instead of marriage
and all other commitments,
just staying together
for emotional needs.
While having a little fun on the side.
Dude!
That sounds like a good option.
Agree to it.
Stop irritating me.
Shut up, damn it.
- Run! Run!
- You're overthinking it.
What about the fling?
It's just about having fun.
I already knew
what living together meant.
The rest are all new to me.
She might be breadcrumbing you.
Meaning...
They won’t seriously commit
but keep you on the hook.
I swear, that’s exactly it.
Give me your hand.
Thank you!
- She’s doing something wrong.
- Score a run.
Don't miss it, Dude.
That was an easy ball.
- Buffalo!
- Look at him play.
Hey, Magic is calling him.
Tell me.
Where are you, Krish?
Did you call me Krish?
That's new.
I’m here with friends.
Why don't you come over to my house?
We have the house to ourselves.
- Go! Go right now!
- Go over there!
Have the house to ourselves?
Yeah, are you coming?
No... No, Magic.
I'm busy with important work.
I'm stuck with something important.
- Hello? Hello?
- Bye, bye, bye, bye.
You're hopeless!
She's definitely not marriage material.
Damn!
What happened?
- Passed!
- Hey!
I don't have a single point
to defend her before Mom.
Oh, no! Are you serious?
Looks like fate has chosen
Uncle's daughter for me.
The daughter, I'm fine with.
But the giggling Uncle is the problem.
Hey, bike taxi, stop.
We've reached home.
- Oh, it's you.
- Get down!
Look, it's embarrassing
he's wearing shoes on his neck.
Like you're royalty or something.
- Get lost!
- Dad!
Are you nuts?
Why are you lashing out at him?
You want to know why?
He got drunk and picked a fight
at the Shalimar entrance.
All my coworkers were there.
Do you know how embarrassed I felt?
I'm a state government employee.
- There he goes again.
- Dear lord in heaven!
What?
Even a state’s CM
wouldn't repeat this phrase so often.
Go away!
Dad, I'm running out of patience.
- Don't test me.
- Shut up!
What do you always call him?
I got it!
What's that? What?
Boomer!
You're a Boomer!
- Get lost for real!
- Dad!
What are you doing?
- Get it together, Dad.
- Why would you push him?
You're unnecessarily causing a problem.
I'll kill you!
Lovely shot!
4 runs!
What are you doing?
How dare you raise your hand on him?
I will kill you myself!
- Mom, it was him...
- I know everything. Get inside.
Go!
Honey...
Come inside.
Dad!
It's been a long time
since love has bloomed between us.
Let me have it.
I have something important to ask you.
- I want to love, damn it!
- Come on!
Tell me. What is it?
It's something important.
Are you sober enough?
I'm the most sober when I'm drunk.
However...
you can’t expect me to recall
our conversation in the morning.
I would have already forgotten by then.
Whatever!
Let's say I'm in love.
Really?
My son!
Not actually, though.
But if I did...
What kind of girl should I fall for?
Your family can’t find
a single fault in her.
Yes! Perfect! Super!
Should be their only responses.
Don’t end up like your old man.
Fell in love with a different caste girl
and still live to regret it
by drowning in alcohol.
Instead of being in a loveless marriage...
Why not fight for what you love?
Then she should have been brave
like my Sarala.
Did you see
how she defended me back there?
But my Ex-lover!
While I was getting beaten up
by her Dad and mine.
All she did was watch.
Hey, Mental!
Then why get drunk every day,
sulking over her?
Hey!
That's what love is.
You won’t get it.
Just don't fall in love, though.
Your mom would never approve.
Not in a million years.
But the way she called me honey, though.
Your wedding is next month...
It’s too late to talk about love,
you moron!
You may be onto something, Dad.
Love isn't in the cards for me.
Wonderland?
I can’t handle the suspense.
She’s here!
- Hi!
Why are we suddenly meeting here?
Like you said during college days...
all important news
must be shared here in Wonderland.
Important news?
Yes, it's a matter of love.
Love matter?
Yeah, man!
There's an Anglo guy
who lives on my street.
He always checks me out.
On the street and at the church.
You probably know him.
Clifton?
I have seen him during cricket practice.
He proposed to me.
What?!
Huh?
He proposed to you?
Keep going.
Yeah!
He said that since we both
want to move to Australia.
It'll be perfect.
So, he asked me to marry him.
One minute, Magic.
Yes!
Jesus! You saved me!
Jesus! I can't express my happiness!
Poor thing. He got possessive.
Yes!
Hey, bugger!
Are you upset?
I've told you from the beginning.
We’re just friends.
I can't hold back my emotions, Magic.
You're doing what you think is right.
But...
Your happiness is all that matters to me.
Aww! You are so sweet!
Indeed, it's sweet.
Shall I tell you how he proposed?
No, Magic.
You need to listen.
He started with a poem.
Poem?
In Tamil, you call it, Kavithai.
It's pronounced "Po-em."
Poem!
Okay, tell me
My love.
In this fast-paced world...
the only face
that brings me peace is yours.
From the moment I saw you...
the directions of my heart
changed completely.
This is not just love.
This is a promise.
This is not just a moment's feeling.
This is a lifetime decision.
I--
That's what he told me.
Whether it’s Australia...
Or America
there’s someone waiting for me
all these years.
I told him
he’s the one I'm going to marry.
I want to marry you, Krishna.
I love you!
♪ You're done, Buddy! ♪
♪ I'm trapped beyond escape ♪
♪ Everything keeps piling up ♪
♪ Every nerve tingles ♪
♪ I've been hit hard by love ♪
♪ She's got me chasing after her ♪
Hey, stop that song!
It's pissing me off!
Did you really think
it would be that easy?
It'll happen
when you least expect it.
Life always throws you for a loop.
You asked for it, didn't you?
Now, pay the price!
- Get lost!
- Hit me!
Hit me all you want.
But you're going endure it, Bro!
I told you to get lost!
- He's irking me.
- Dude, let him go.
Think about your next move.
Like I'd know!
I have no clue!
Then do what I say.
Imagine if she moved into your home
after you married.
Think long and hard about it.
Hey! What kind of dress is this?
Modern dress, Mom.
What?
What meat are you cooking?
Beef, Auntie!
Your son got it from the meat market
early in the morning.
Beef!
What, Mummy?
It’s for a nuptial ritual, dear.
Show me your nuptial chain.
Krishna, I must have left it
in the hanger. Get it for me.
One minute, Auntie!
You just doomed my fate.
You can hang it back there.
Krishna!
What?
Sing!
Oh, no, no!
Praise the lord, my son.
Cheers!
- Cheers, Daughter-in-law.
- Cheers, Uncle.
Cheers!
Sarala, would you like some?
It's delicious!
Krishna!
I can't even imagine this happening.
What would happen
if I introduce her as my fiance?
What do you think?
Either you leave your home for her.
Which you probably won't do.
They might just kick you out of the house.
Which is more likely to happen.
You're not helping.
Dude, I'm repeating now.
You're worrying over nothing.
All she did was confess her love.
She's a modern girl.
Based on what you told us...
she's not the type
to get tied down by marriage.
She might date you for a few days
and then break up.
What makes you so sure?
Because I know everything
about Anglos--
Do you even have to ask?
Like you mentioned
if she's not the marrying type I'm happy.
My Uncle is already planning an engagement.
Hey, it's Magic.
Hello, Magic!
Krish, Where are you?
I'm at Baba's shop.
I told my Dad about our relationship.
He wants to see you immediately.
Could you come over
to my house tomorrow?
Dude, was I right?
Because I know everything
about Anglos--
Shut your trap!
If I hear you repeat that phrase,
I'll kill you.
Were they relatives?
They look really fair.
Magic.
Why did you act in haste
and tell your father?
I haven't told him yet.
But you have to.
Haven't you told him yet?
Then, why did you make me come over?
I lied so that you came.
Would you have come otherwise?
Go and tell him.
Magic, why are we rushing into this?
We still have a time left.
I already told you.
That Clifton proposed to me.
Yesterday, he also proposed to my father.
What?!
He proposed to your dad, too?
- Eww!
- Oh, God!
Marriage proposal!
If you keep avoiding my Dad
with these lame jokes...
he'll drag me to Australia as his wife.
Magic, please hear me out--
No more arguments!
Shut up and do as I say.
Come with me.
Follow me!
What's in a name?
That which we call a rose
by any other name.
Smells just as sweet...
What is he doing?
...as candy!
He's rehearsing for an English play.
- Dad?
- Yes, my dear!
Krishna wants to talk to you.
Yes, Krishna. Tell me.
I'm all ears!
I don't understand
I meant
I'm ready to hear you out.
Oh, ah, okay!
I don't know how to begin, Uncle...
You see...
The thing is...
I'm in love with your daughter, Uncle.
And you, Magic?
Yes, Dad. I love him too.
I like him so much.
Uncle...
I get it, Uncle.
No father would approve this--
I approve!
Uncle?
I don't understand.
I approve of your relationship.
If you two like each other.
Who am I to get in the way?
Uncle...
Why did you have to say yes?
What?!
Did you approve
because I'm a good boy?
Not even close.
What I'm trying to say is...
It’s the faith
I have in my daughter.
If we don't trust our children,
who else will?
Why, Krishna?
Doesn't your family trust you?
Sure, they trust me.
They trust me like crazy!
See, anyway,
I'm fine with you two marrying.
But I have one condition.
I want my daughter
to have a Grand church wedding.
That's all!
I can't convert my religion, Uncle.
I never asked you to convert.
There's a marriage class
you need to attend for 10 days.
Only if you attend it
they will issue a certificate
to get married in a church.
Aww! Thanks, Dad.
- Are you happy, child?
- Yeah.
Hey, Bugger, are you happy?
Overjoyed, Magic!
Okay, come,
let's get him something to eat.
Yeah, sure.
Christ Almighty!
Dude, when will you tell your family?
Like that will change anything.
- How much longer?
- Mummy! Mummy!
My dear son.
You look great in the shirt.
Thanks, Mom.
Now, where is this Mangababu?
It’s getting late.
Big sis!
Here I am!
He never changes.
Look at your Uncle.
What is all this?
- All for my son-in-law.
- Wow!
- Your uncle is really fond of you.
- Hand it to me.
Tanisha, sit close to the air conditioning.
- He's torturing me.
- Son-in-law.
- Uncle.
- You’re still pretty young.
Over the years,
you might have run out of fuel.
So if you’re looking for nourishment.
That’s what these cashews and nuts are for.
Foolish Uncle!
Don’t be gross!
Are you such a pure soul, my son?
So innocent!
Tanisha, you’re very lucky!
Decorations are totally awesome!
Hey, kid. Go over there.
Dude, get over here.
Come on!
Hey, BulBul!
Go sit in a corner
You are not the Groom today.
- Uncle.
- Stop looking and get up.
Just go!
- Insult! I'm totally angry.
- Him and his style.
Son-in-law, you sit in the middle.
Tanisha, sit next to him.
Closer!
What’s with his nagging?
Big sis, hurry up.
The groom is waiting.
Quick!
- Hurry up!
- Hey, Mangababu!
Your son-in-law is not going anywhere.
Quit hopping!
Sit down.
Yeah, Okay
My son-in-law neck looks empty.
- That's for the ceremony!
- Okay, fine.
Oh, God!
Shut up for once
Listen!
I am going to the station!
Hey, no need to yell!
- I'm wearing the machine.
- Cool! Cool!
Why are you coming with me?
Are you sending away
your daughter today?
I can travel by Auto.
While the bride and groom
can ride together.
Good idea!
Drop her off, Son.
Your uncle is calling for you.
Come along.
Go ahead, Son.
Him too? Whatever!
Bye!
- Monkey! Sit inside.
- Bye, sweetie.
I am so happy today, darling.
Darling!
I love you.
What’s wrong?
Please get down.
What for?
Get down!
What happened, dude?
Dude, don’t take this the wrong way.
But could you drop her off instead?
Something came up.
I need to leave now.
He will drop you at the station.
Don't take me wrong.
- Dude, drop her off.
- Me?
- Uncle, second ball.
- Hey, wait, wait.
- Hello!
- Hey, Krish!
- Yes, Magic. What’s up?
- Hey, Man!
Can you come over
for like 10 minutes?
There is a house party at Barbara's place.
Would you like to join?
I’m in the middle of something important.
- So, I can’t make it.
- Important, you say?
Yeah, exactly!
Magic, I’ll call you later.
- I'll call you back.
- It won’t take more than 10 minutes.
I’ll finish work and call later.
Hello.
He seems distant
after the talk with my Dad.
I have no idea what’s going on with him.
Dude!
If you don't like her,
you have to end it.
You can’t drag this out forever.
It’s frustrating!
I can’t say no to her either.
I am not able to muster the courage
to say it.
Sometimes, when I look at her...
She’s a spitting image of my mother.
Sorry.
What’s going on with you?
There’s a tryout
for a government coach, Magic.
I was tied up with the exam preparations.
Okay, I can understand.
Don't stress too much, okay?
Okay.
I love you.
Thanks.
I said I’d take care of it.
Quit pestering me.
I’m trusting you on this.
I will take care of it.
Yeah, okay.
You have nothing to worry about.
Stop, Uncle!
Leave him alone!
- How many times should I tell you?
- Uncle!
I’ll kill you!
He’s already engaged to another woman.
Yet stringing you along.
Don't you have any sense?
Auto! Come over here.
Get in!
- Uncle.
- Get inside!
You too!
Sis, I caught the love birds!
I’ll meet you back at the police station.
Sir!
- Hey, Baba.
- Greetings, Baba.
- Everything is fine, sir.
- One minute.
Baba, brother!
Oh! What's she doing here?
Brother, I want to ask you something.
Will you tell me the truth?
I’ll tell you what I know.
Krishna has been avoiding me.
He is not telling me anything, either.
What happened to him?
Would you prefer the truth or the lie?
I’ve been told
that Bangalore people don’t lie.
He will never marry you.
He’s going to break up with you.
What are you saying?
Because you're not the right fit for him.
Not the right fit? Why not?
Well, you look quite modern.
You wear tiny shorts.
Can’t hold your liquor.
You dance with other men.
There was something else.
What was it?
I can’t remember.
Got it!
That you hug people head on.
Since those things don't suit his family.
He is going to break up with you.
Brother, don’t make things up.
Tell me the truth.
Without you doing it all...
how would I know
if he didn’t tell me?
All I'm saying is...
he is going to break up with you.
It's without a doubt.
Where is he now?
At home!
What are you going to do with it?
Oh, no!
Baba, this cover is not right.
Get lost!
It's not the Champions League.
Magic! What are you doing here?
Hey!
Magic, have you lost it?
What are you doing?
Does our feelings mean nothing to you?
You will follow us for years
till we fall in love.
But the second we reciprocate...
You break up, citing
that it won't suit your family.
If you can't commit to a relationship.
Why the heck do you fall in love
in the first place?
Who told you that?
Hey, she's...
If your family disapproved--
Who told you this?
Who told you
that I’d break up with you?
It was me!
I can’t take responsibility
for a blabber mouth.
I know how to stay loyal.
Did you ask me?
Did you ask me before lashing out?
I did not.
You are-- You are right.
I probably should have asked you.
Yes, you should have!
Instead, you're smashing the television.
Oh, no!
Sorry
Really sorry, Krishna!
I overreacted.
- Sorry!
- Forget it!
Listen here, Magic.
You can’t let a third person
come between us.
Brother, why didn’t you--
Magic!
You don't have to ask anyone else.
There's no need.
Trust me, first.
Your lack of trust caused this.
That’s a complete 180.
- Sorry, Krishna. My bad.
- Too late!
- I'm sorry, Krishna.
- You don't trust me.
- Let it go.
- Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry, Bugger!
We’re cool!
Hi, Magic!
Hi Bommi, how are you?
- Why do you do this, Dude?
- Fine!
Is no one else home?
Where is everyone?
Did they all go out somewhere?
Please don't tell her.
Don't tell her.
Don't say anything.
Please don't say anything.
Since Krishna Uncle’s...
Fiance came over last week for the feast.
So it’s our family’s turn
to go over to their house for a feast.
Game over!
Magic, I can explain--
Damn it, you bugger!
- Magic!
- It wasn't me.
Magic!
Are you mad or what?
Sorry, dude!
She brought it out of me.
Mom, I keep telling you
I don't want anything.
Why are you irritating me like this?
Please leave me alone for once.
Please!
- Hello!
- Darling!
I’m sorry if I offended you.
I shouldn’t have said what I said.
It’s nothing like that.
It was my fault. Sorry!
Why are you apologizing?!
Please don't apologize!
I’m coming to Chennai tomorrow.
Can you show me around?
Is Marina Beach always clean?
Or there are a lot of stones...
Tanisha...
The only thing modern about her
is her name.
So you don’t like it
if they’re modern.
And you don’t like it
if they’re not.
Do you even know what you want?
Clifton...
I can't decide yet.
I think I need some more time.
Maybe this is for the best, Dude.
You were going to do it yourself.
Time to move on!
I indeed thought about it.
But there's a way to do it.
Maybe she doesn't fit into my family.
But I never stopped loving her.
I’ve said all I can.
And I can’t keep dodging
my Mom’s questions.
Dad, did you shave your beard?
Mom, can you turn on
the grinder for me?
- Bommi! I ought to!
- Sathya!
Please, Mom
You switch it on. I'll be there.
Yay!
Don’t deflect your anger towards me
onto the child.
I can’t move out of my parents’ house.
Period.
I can’t just abandon my mother.
Imagine yourself in my shoes.
Then abandon the two of us.
What? What do you mean?
Where do you want me to go?
Where the hell am I supposed to go?
What happened?
Did he say something?
It’s not his fault.
It’s my own.
Hey!
Neither here nor there.
Each day,
I feel increasingly conflicted.
The fault is my own.
If you like something,
you need to fight for it.
Or you should let it go.
But I can't seem to decide on anything.
Sathya!
I'm struggling with it.
Hey, idiot!
Stop crying.
He’s also at fault here.
No!
He likes me too much.
He’s struggling without me
by his side.
Caught between his mom and me.
Look here...
that’s not for you to decide.
Let him do it.
He doesn't need to.
You can see it in their actions.
When someone really likes us...
and they realize they’d be miserable
without us
they'll definitely come back to us.
One day or another
hoping that we'll forgive
and take them back.
Magic!
Sorry, Magic.
I never meant to hurt you.
Dear, Jesus!
I committed a grave sin
by hurting my lover.
Please forgive me
and get her to talk to me.
You sound foolish
when you try to act smart.
I'm enraged enough to break your teeth.
If you have shame, stay away.
Jesus, what was that?
Hi, Magic!
What the heck do you want,
you bloody bugger?
Don't make me smack you.
I have no pride left in me.
No matter what you say or do...
I won't leave your side.
Hey!
What the hell do you want?
Do you think you’re some hero?
Do you think
I won’t make a scene in public?
Driver, stop the bus!
You'd better get off the bus now.
Or else, you'll be humiliated
beyond your imagination.
Now, do you realize
how it hurts to be rejected?
That's how it feels when you're
humiliated in public for love.
That's how I was feeling the other day.
I never meant to hurt you.
I shouldn't have done that either.
Sorry!
I'm too sorry, Magic.
I shouldn't have hurt you.
I was worried you wouldn’t fit
into my family--
See, Krishna!
I know our families don’t share
the same culture.
If you were worried about how I’d fit in...
You should have asked me first.
But how is that possible?
You can try to adapt to my culture.
While I try to adapt to your family.
Or we could move out.
And lead our own lives.
Isn’t that what love is?
Sorry, Magic.
Really sorry, Magic.
Apologies from the bottom of my heart.
From here on out...
You’ll be the one I marry.
Please, Magic.
Sorry, Magic.
Trust me.
One last chance, Magic
- Last chance--
- What about your fiancé?
We were never meant to be.
She’s better off with someone else.
I’ll confront my family.
With all the courage I can muster.
That I like Magic.
Can I trust you this time?
Trust me, one last chance please.
Last chance, you bugger.
Thank you, Magic!
You need to tell our Mom
about my love.
Hey, why me?
Oh, no! Please spare me.
Didn't you agree to help me back then?
That was an isolated event.
I can't go through with it.
No way!
- Not happening.
- Please, please.
- I said please.
- Hey!
Chiranjeevi might be able to
persuade Mom.
Who are you again?
Hey!
Just hear me out first.
And why should I?
When have you ever listened to me?
Ma’am, check this.
Here you go.
Didn’t I tell you
to take that government exam?
You're talking irrelevant
to what I'm about to say.
I will talk irrelevant!
If you'd like then listen.
On second thought, don’t.
Get out of my office!
Hey!
Get out!
Why are you worried?
I can talk to your Mom.
Seriously?
Yeah, why not!
I'm not scared of her.
Can you run it by me once?
For God’s sake, I’m not a child.
I’ll tell her myself.
Wait, wait!
My Mom will never believe
that I’m in love.
Don't add too much water.
Auntie, how are you?
All good?
I’m doing just fine.
What brought you here?
Just wanted to tell you something.
What is it about?
Our boy Krishna
is in love with a girl.
Love?!
Who's the girl?
I’m glad you asked.
She looks like an actress.
Take a look, Auntie.
Our boy’s got good taste.
She’s pretty, isn’t she?
You can't say no to her.
Good choice, right?
I tried to warn you.
My Mom will never believe
that I’m in love.
It’s true that your Mom never bought it.
But not the part about you being in love.
It was the fact
that any girl would love you back.
It hurts to laugh.
Hilarious!
Dad!
I’m in love with a girl.
What?
Love?
You?
Really?
Fantastic news!
Dad, about the girl...
The one you spoke about the other day.
Exactly, Dad!
If you can meet her first...
then I can introduce her to Mom.
Why wait?
I’ll meet her tomorrow.
Super, Dad.
Dad still remembers
that the girl is Anglo-Indian.
Superb!
Just like he said...
looks like he found a girl
from our caste.
Magic, that's my dad.
Brother, that's a fantastic song.
Dad!
- [in Telugu] How are you, dear?
- I'll get us tea.
Uncle?
[in Telugu] I asked How are you doing?
Uncle, I don’t understand Telugu.
I assumed a girl from our caste
would speak Telugu.
How could you assume
I belong to your caste?
Son...
Isn’t she one of us?
Dad!
She’s an Anglo-Indian!
Can’t you tell from the way she looks?
It can’t be an Anglo-Indian!
Hey!
Did you throw a challenge the other day?
I was clearly bluffing.
That doesn't mean you take it seriously
and act on it.
Dad!
These people cannot adapt
to our family's culture.
- Please hear me out--
- And who are you to decide that?
You're meeting me for the first time.
You only have the right
to approve or reject me.
Instead don't judge
or assume things on my behalf.
Now, do you approve or not?
What’s your verdict?
My dear son...
What your mother is to me.
She is to you.
Men like us are bound to end up
with women like her.
Thanks, Uncle!
Let’s have some coffee.
- Phew!
- Dad!
Could you also tell mom about this?
As if!
Dad!
It won’t be that easy.
First we need to change her
for your Mom.
Change what?
Why are you always on the edge?
I was just asking, Uncle.
Is this the tone you always speak in?
Never mind, Dad. Tell us what to do.
His mom considers her caste and creed
as the most important aspects.
I reckon it doesn't matter to you.
My dear!
Since it's new to you,
try to get the hang of it.
Dad!
- This will never work out.
- It’s fine, Krish.
I can learn.
My father too asked you to attend
the marriage classes.
We’ll learn each others cultures.
Love is all about adapting, right?
Let's learn!
Cheers, dear!
Cheers, Uncle.
♪ We're a match made in heaven ♪
♪ No match could be finer ♪
♪ Here we are,
Writing a brand-new love story. ♪
♪ Love robs me of sleep ♪
Krishna Benjamin
Magic Gonsalves
I’m glad to have you both here.
♪ As I seek my way ♪
♪ Every path finds you ♪
♪ Somehow, magic and miracles entwined ♪
You should see the lengths
she goes to for Mom’s approval.
I was too quick to judge her.
That’s great!
- When are you going to tell Mom?
- Hey!
Can you tell her instead?
You’re on your own!
♪ Wedding bells fill the air ♪
♪ Even butterflies found their soulmates ♪
♪ Two hearts have become one ♪
♪ Hare Rama...
What a beautiful madness ♪
♪ Wedding bells fill the air ♪
[Prayer] "Om Vigna Vinayaka Pada Namaste."
Coming 8th is Ammavasai.
What’s that?
It means no moon day.
And Povurnami is a full moon day.
This book will tell you
how to use this rosary.
Hey! What’s all this?
She is in a spiritual awakening.
[Chanting Prayer]
♪ Wedding bells fill the air ♪
♪ Even butterflies found their soulmates ♪
♪ Two hearts have become one ♪
♪ Hare Rama...
What a beautiful madness ♪
That’s it!
You’re almost ready.
Tomorrow is Sashti.
No, Uncle.
Sashti isn’t tomorrow.
It’s Pradosham.
Fantastic!
- She's fantastic.
- Well done!
You will definitely pass the test.
You come to the temple tomorrow.
We'll break the new over there.
She has to say yes.
Don’t you worry.
Okay, Uncle.
Don’t forget to wear the outfit I chose.
Okay, done!
Hey!
That was our thing.
This is a surprise.
I’ve never seen you here before.
We wanted to pray?
Start praying.
Really?
Do you expect me to believe that?
Time is running out.
She’ll be here soon.
Whatever!
Dad she's here.
Come on, dear.
Come!
You look stunning in a saree.
You’re just in the nick of time.
She just started the rounds.
After the 8th round,
she'll halt right there.
Fall at her feet, right then and there.
She won’t get angry at that time.
All the best!
Thank you, Uncle.
Okay, carry on.
Hang on a second...
How did you figure out
Mom won't get angry out there?
Cause that’s where I told her
of my old love.
You’re hopeless!
Fall at her feet.
Do it!
Please, Magic.
Bless me, aunty.
Mom...
This is my lover, Revathy.
Lover?!
Oh, no!
Hey, Chiranjeevi!
What do you mean?
She is one of us, Mom.
Oh! Our caste?
I’m glad!
Even in love...
you stayed loyal to your caste.
I’m very happy!
Thanks, Mom!
What does your father do, Dear?
Her father is my office head.
It's her daughter.
He never changes!
Super!
Mom!
This is...
This is my lover.
Her name is...
Her name...
Magic!
Magic Gonsalves.
Go for it
Bless me too, Auntie.
Who gave you permission
to fall in love?
And with Christian--
I can't even pronounce her name.
Where did you even find her?
Mom, we just came from the temple.
I can't eat egg now...
Learn from him.
I’m proud to call him my son.
He kept his family in mind
while falling in love.
I can never refuse him.
Thanks, Mom!
Good son!
Mom, Magic is alike.
She even wore a saree for your sake.
Wearing a saree won't change
one's religion.
Zip it!
If you keep talking
I’ll kill you myself.
It’s not like that, Mom.
Just meet her once.
She's a good girl.
Shush!
I've already spoken.
There’s nothing more to say.
How will I explain it to my niece?
Besides...
What will he say to his father-in-law?
That his brother is marrying
a Christian girl?
You should be ashamed!
Sarala!
What?
You go along with all of his whims.
But deny all his requests.
Is he your only son?
Isn’t he your son, too?
You can’t judge someone
without meeting them first.
We are going tomorrow.
We are meeting them.
- And you must come along!
- But...
Say nothing!
You too!
But I didn’t speak.
Especially you!
Quiet!
Dad...
How did you find courage while still sober?
I have no idea.
I just went with the flow.
- Was that okay?
- Okay?!
You just nailed it, Dad!
Mom will definitely come along.
No, she won't.
Come on, Dad!
Hey, I know all about her.
I’ll convince her somehow.
I know how to tackle your mother.
Tell them we’ll be there tomorrow.
Can I really trust you?
Trust me!
You look like a clown in that coat.
You’re going to stick out
like a sore thumb.
It’s fine, Mom--
Take it off!
Mom, it looks good!
Where are we now?
It’s her cousin's wedding.
- Hello, Uncle.
- Hey!
- Hi, Aunty
- Hi.
Come, let's go. It'll be fun.
Go!
Let's go!
Hi!
♪ You wake up early ♪
♪ I stay up late ♪
♪ I say relax ♪
♪ You say we're late ♪
♪ You fill my stomach ♪
♪ You fill my heart ♪
♪ We're stuck together ♪
♪ Till death do us part ♪
See who has come.
Don’t go, man. Come back here.
Come back!
Dad!
Stop!
Why did you just storm out?
I’ll support you marrying any girl...
But not his daughter.
Why’s that?
I asked you a question!
Because he’s the reason I lost my hearing!
Huh?
Hey, Ron!
Take over for my section, too.
Finish all my work, too.
What’s with the look?
Do you refuse?
Why?
Why should I do your work for you?
Go do it yourself, man.
Hey!
Are you ganging up on me?
You guys are just temporary.
You won't keep your job for long.
What happened, man?
He's going to get whacked by me.
He's been poking me unnecessarily.
I'm a key member of the union.
They shouldn’t have messed with me.
So, I got them all fired as I mentioned.
Let go of me!
Don't you dare!
Aren't you even ashamed?
Someone has beaten up your Dad.
And the others laughed him out of the room.
And you’re just staring at them.
You’re no son of mine.
Damn you!
Relax! Relax!
It’s alright. Come on!
Dad!
What the hell are you doing, Bugger?!
Hey!
I know exactly what I'm doing.
You should ask him what happened!
Nothing matters more to me
than my Dad.
I don't want you anymore in my life.
Hey!
Stop!
Krishna!
I've never seen a bigger idiot than you.
Why? What did I do?
You fell right into your Mom’s trap.
And you started a fight!
Do you think you're some kind of a hero?
Nothing matters more to me
than my Dad.
You really are a fool.
Hey, Bhaskar!
My patience is running thin.
Then what?
If I had waited 5 minutes,
I would've calmed down.
What happened that day
was my own fault?
Krishna...
Your only chance at happiness...
is if you marry Magic.
That’s all I have to say.
But, Mom has to agree to that.
That girl has to agree, first.
Apologize and make peace.
We'll deal with your Mom later.
Dad!
I don't want to talk to
any buggers out here!
Uncle...
I didn't mean for it
to get out of hand.
I'm terribly sorry, Uncle.
It's okay, Krishna.
Huh?
No son would have reacted differently.
I would have done the same thing, as well.
I had no idea he lost his hearing
because of me.
I feel very bad about it.
I'm sorry, Krishna.
My apologies to you...
your dad and to your entire family.
Oh, wow!
I’m glad you guys made peace.
Very good!
Not reason enough to marry you.
What else do you want him to do,
Magic?
That's his line.
He needs to ask that question.
Okay, tell me.
What should I do now?
Can you convince your Mom?
Will you leave that house for me
if she doesn't approve?
Why?
Is it impossible to marry someone
with their parent's approval?
What’s stopping you?
Do it! If you can!
Don't face me again
until you convince your Mom.
Or else don't come to my house ever.
You coward Bugger!
Magic...
Krishna!
Take as long as you want.
But I'm moving to Australia next week.
My visa has been confirmed.
Quit asking me the same thing.
Like I said before.
Engagement doesn't have to be
a separate expense.
It can be the same as reception.
Why should I ask Krishna?
What I say goes around here!
It's not like he can decide anyway.
Hey, Mangababu!
Inform all our people.
I want all of them to attend the wedding.
Understood?
This ends tonight
- Dad, don't.
- Let me go!
You don't bring up new things.
Understood?
Are you even human?!
Let me call you back.
I just want to know!
What kind of a human are you?
Are you going to stay like this forever?
Are you the only authority in this house?
Always grumpy.
Yelling at everyone.
You might as well be Hitler!
Why are you always so obsessed
with caste?
Did you ever think about
your son's happiness?
Cause she values her caste
over her own children.
Hey, Krishna!
Yes, indeed!
My people are important to me.
I never cared about my children.
Nor do I care about this family?
Is that what you want to hear?
- Mom?
- What?!
I may have a temper.
Have you wondered,
what made me this way?
Your Dad here...
...is a railway employee for namesake.
Ever since you were a kids...
he burns away his entire salary
on friends, food and drinking.
In fact, he’s still the same.
If I'm not the way that I am...
we could never have raised
all 3 kids and built this house.
We would have ended up
on the streets.
Have you ever treated me
as your wife?
You won't even look me in the eye.
You can't!
Because everything you do
is immoral.
Wrong!
You want to know
why I stay loyal to my community?
When we were dead broke...
the one who loaned us the money
to start my flour shop
was someone from my caste!
Without them,
we won't have this house.
Do you get it now?
They may have helped you
start the shop.
But not the one who kept it running.
♪ A single drop of your love
Is enough to fill my heart ♪
♪ Every dream I've cherished
Becomes reality ♪
♪ A single smile is enough
To make a petal bloom ♪
♪ All the pain in my heart
Melts away ♪
♪ Beneath the endless sky,
Life unfolds before us ♪
♪ In the end... ♪
♪ Only a love that never runs dry
Remains between us ♪
♪ You're the guiding star ♪
♪ That shines your light upon me ♪
♪ A radiant glow ♪
♪ You're the raindrop... ♪
♪ Yet the moment you touch me, ♪
♪ You become an endless ocean ♪
How much is in there?
50,000.
Come on, now!
I brought 10 people with me.
Everyone in our group was afraid
to voice opinions against.
- I went to a lot of trouble.
- I will pay you later.
Check if they're here.
Will do!
Bommi, behave!
They’re here, brother.
Bring them in.
- Leave everything to us.
- Bommi! Slow down!
Granny, did you eat?
- Hey!
- What the hell, Mom?
I'm warning you.
She's like a child.
- Dad, I'm leaving.
- Sathya, you stay.
Look at her.
Everybody, take a look.
Who wouldn't get mad over this?
And when I called her a nutcase,
she left the house.
Why do you think?
Meena, she's just a child.
Yes, indeed!
It’s not like I tortured her.
I only told them to try again
for a good child.
What's wrong with that?
What do you mean by "Good child?"
Isn't she a good child?
Look here...
- Do you know what mild autism is?
- Brother!
I don't need anymore lectures.
Your daughter
has already taken enough classes.
Now decide the next move.
The next move?
It’s to live together.
To reunite the family.
Isn't that why all our folks
have gathered around.
For that, she needs to come back
to our house.
That's right.
Sarala, your daughter,
should be the one to move out.
If she stays at your house,
what can we do?
If this is how they act in public...
there is no saying
what they might do in private.
My sister will only come back
if it’s an individual household.
Hey!
What's your sister's problem?
Always insisting on a separate family
It just sounds suspicious.
Watch your tongue!
I’ll beat him to a pulp.
Let go of him.
Get away from him.
Have you lost your mind?
What are you doing?
It's wrong to hit your elders.
- Did he act like an elder?
- That's enough!
That’s enough!
We didn't gather here
to see you guys fighting.
Sarala, will your daughter
go to their house?
If it’s a separate household,
I’ll send her right away.
I won't throw her to the wolves
Dear lord in heaven!
Shankar, are you seeing this?
They're making me look like the villain.
Aren't you?
- Shankar!
- Mom!
This is your life.
You take it from here.
- I'm leaving!
- Mom!
Mom!
Good riddance!
She’s such a drama queen.
- Mom, get back over here.
- Let go of me.
- Please hear me out.
- Let go of her!
Let her leave.
How would we come to a solution
if you leave?
Look here...
there nothing more to say.
She can come back home,
if she wants to.
Or let’s agree on a mutual divorce.
What?
Son in law?!
What are you even suggesting?
This wasn’t the reason
I married her within our community.
No matter what happens,
we'd adjust among ourselves.
Auntie, why do you still cling to caste?
It doesn’t matter.
What matters is a person’s character.
If their character is bad,
how does caste help in that matter?
Shankar has a point.
Character is what matters.
You can’t hide behind caste.
So that's why Sarala ends each sentence
with Our people.
We stand on the side of justice.
That’s the loyalty we owe to our caste.
Caste isn't a means to escape.
Send over your daughter
or agree to a mutual divorce.
We'll find another wife for Shankar.
There's plenty of other girls.
Hey!
My niece is close by.
I can talk to her--
Get out!
- Sarala?
- Say what?
Get the hell out, you dogs!
Show some respect.
Someone who separates a family
for money doesn't deserve respect.
Get out of here!
- Get lost!
- Alright, you heard her. Let's go
This is the end of this committee.
What do you want?
What do you want!?
If you want your wife and child
Stop listening to her
and live your own lives.
Or else...
Do you need him?
Not if he's going to stay like this.
You heard her.
Go away!
- What?
- Get the hell out!
You can always remarry.
Shut up, mom!
You're the cause of all this.
I know.
I'll live my own life.
Enough!
Why, Mom?
Sarala...
Why did you antagonize our son-in-law?
Then what should I have done?
Does he make a decision on his own?
If he just keeps living for his mother...
What about his life?
He likes Sathya, right?
Why not just leave his mother behind?
You’re against your son-in-law doing this.
But isn't your son doing the same thing.
You feel it when you're daughter suffers.
But you don't care about the other girl.
What can I do now?
The wedding is in two weeks.
It's too late now.
What am I supposed to do?
What if it was earlier?
Okay, he didn't.
But why couldn't he?
We never had
that sort of an environment.
We expect our children to be obedient.
But think about
how we actually treat that obedient kid.
Then you'll understand.
Big sis!
My dear, sister!
There he comes!
Oh, there you are!
Brother-in-law is here too.
Saves me the trouble.
Here's the wedding invite.
Check it out!
For god's sake!
I still can't read Telugu!
I forgot about that.
Sis, I handed the invitation
to all our folks back home.
I brought some Telugu invitations
in case there's anyone here.
Tanisha is very happy
Wedding hall has been fixed.
Catering has been fixed.
Live music has been fixed.
♪ Won't this aching pain of love
Ever fade away? ♪
♪ I ask
Through my tears ♪
♪ Isn't your disdain enough
To break me? ♪
♪ With each passing day ♪
♪ I'm unraveling ♪
♪ I'm losing myself ♪
♪ With every breath I have ♪
♪ I fill my soul with you ♪
♪ Will this go on forever? ♪
♪ Or will it finally end? ♪
♪ I'm breaking apart ♪
♪ Piece by piece ♪
♪ Will the deepest part of me ♪
♪ Ever learn to hate you? ♪
Hey, Baba!
Tell me, Dude!
I need a small favor.
What, dude?
Do you plan to run away
from the wedding?
And you want me to sneak you out.
Magic is waiting in her car
at the end of this street.
Like hell!
Don't make me lose my temper.
I think you already did.
What's the favor?
I asked my brother to get me some shoes.
Look at what he got me.
I need something casual.
To go with the suit.
Can you get me that?
I thought you might commit suicide
after losing Magic.
But I’m glad you found
a compromise with your shoes.
You’re great, Dude!
Don't test me.
My rage is at its peak and I'd kill you.
Walk away!
- Carry them one by one.
- Come on, hurry up!
- It's getting late. Hurry up!
- Where is your husband?
He's upstairs.
He isn't responding.
- I'll go get him.
- Fine, try.
You look great!
Like an action star.
- Stop torturing him.
- I forgot about it.
I'll get your Dad.
Wait, I'll bring him down.
Be quick about it.
It's almost time
He'll take care of it.
You do your work.
Dad?
This isn't going resolve anything.
Even I moved on!
Dad?
Hey!
Bhaskar, wake up!
You look like you've seen a ghost.
You scared me for a second, Dad.
I thought you died cause I lost Magic.
What?
If you can't marry your lover...
Maybe you should die.
Why should I?
You don’t have the guts
to convince your mother.
Were you counting on on my death
to stop the wedding?
Hey, Bhaskar!
Watch yourself.
My rage is at its peak.
Hey!
If you spoke to your mother this way
Magic would have been the bride.
Not her.
Your fate is sealed!
Nobody can stop this wedding!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
Oh, God!
Hey move aside.
- Don't cry!
- What’s wrong?
Hey, Mangababu!
Why are you crying?
What happened?
I lost her for good.
Lost who?
Your daughter is just moving
into our house.
You haven’t lost her.
Wear the damn machine!
Watch your tone!
Now, tell me.
My daughter is missing.
All I found was a letter in her room.
Read it out!
Big sis!
We'll handle it.
Hey!
For the last time,
I can’t read Telugu!
Read it for yourself!
But I can't to read any language.
For God’s sake!
Give that back.
Mom you read this.
- Oh no!
- What?!
What happened , Mom?
I don’t think this is Telugu.
I think we can guess what’s in there.
Probably that she eloped
with some other guy.
Watch your tongue!
She might have gone out
to get some air.
Do you believe that she went out
to grab a coffee?
You fool!
She ran off with some guy.
Oh, no!
Don't cry, Brother.
Please calm down.
Do you know to read?
Give me a second.
Doesn’t anyone in this family
know how to read?
Krishna will bring her back.
Don't worry!
Dude!
I found the perfect shoe for you.
A perfect match for your coat.
Hang up, you moron!
Oh, no!
What happened, dude?
The girl ran away.
- The girl eloped?
- Yeah!
Then forget about it.
Let’s grab ourselves some tea.
Hey!
Did you hear what I just said?
Dude...
It’s not like being there
is going to solve anything.
Get over here.
You do have a point.
- I'll come.
- Just get here.
She can’t even run properly.
This man I say.
Hey, I need to borrow your bike.
Dude, where are you off to?
The bride ran away.
I see... the bride ran away.
Did you say the bride ran away?
How did it happen
without my knowledge?
Why is he shocked?
Hey!
You damn traitor!
I'm going to kill you.
It’s not what you think, Dude.
It’s true love.
I’ll end you!
We sincerely love each other.
As if!
In 2 weeks?
Dude!
You believed it when Kamal Haasan
said it in Vettaiyaadu Vilaiyaadu.
2 weeks is plenty time.
I’ll kill you!
Did Kamal Hassan run away
with his friend's bride?
I enraged. I'm going to--
Please don't harm him.
I’ll rip out your stupid hair.
I'll kill you!
Boys!
You can’t play here.
Play outside after having tea.
Is my anger a joke to you people?
Do I look like a fool?
I look like a mockery, aren't I?
- You’re the one to blame for this.
- Step aside!
- I ought to!
- Let’s think about our next move.
- I'm going to crack open your head.
- Dude, hear me out.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
This is the end for you!
One Tea!
I’ll kill you!
Auto! Come over here.
Get in!
You too!
Auto!
Get over here!
He’ll help us out.
Are you taking us to get married
at the temple?
Just shut up and get in!
Get in!
You too! Get in!
Thank you, Brother!
What just happened?
Please go to Lord Perumal's temple.
Hey, get out!
I told you to get out!
Hey, step out.
- Don't do it, Dude.
- It’s your funeral!
Dude! Dude!
Please, don't do this.
How dare you run away?
Hey, Mangababu, stop crying and look.
My son and his friend
brought your daughter back.
Hey, they're back!
You’ll have your wedding.
I’ll smack you!
You’re right, Uncle.
We caught her together.
I’ll smack you twice.
Get away!
Where did you run off to?
If it weren’t for this kind soul--
You fool!
This kind soul was the one
who ran off with her.
Baba, It was you!
You got that right!
I'm sorry.
Did he teach you to write
in gibberish Telugu?
That wasn’t Telugu, Uncle.
It’s Kannada!
I wrote that letter
Sorry I made you read it, Brother.
You fool! Get lost!
It’s not like I can read Kannada.
Hey, Mangababu!
Tell us what to do next.
What else?
The bride is back.
Let's get them married!
Oh!
You want me to go through with it?
I must look like a fool to you.
They can marry each other
for all I care!
Dude!
Now you’re speaking in gibberish.
I can't understand.
Are you going to marry her?
As if!
I will marry her myself.
Am I a joke to you?
I asked you to give
her a ride
Not to steal her
You expect me to marry her?
What do you think of me?
I’m not a chump!
I’m ready to throw hands!
Forget about it, Bro!
Chill out!
[in Hindi] Harish, my friend.
Tell me what should I do?
Whatever my family asks of me
I quietly do it.
But look what they have done to me.
Everyone thinks I'm an idiot.
Krishna!
Have you seen Magic?
She’s late for her flight.
I can’t find her.
Oh, really?
You can't find her, Uncle?
You can’t find her--
Yeah, I have her in my pockets.
See!
I got her right here!
You’re just mocking me, aren’t you?
I lost her, Uncle.
Because I lacked the guts
to tell my family that I need her.
Now, I lost her.
I'm a bugger!
Stupid bugger as Magic says.
My son...
I’m sorry, I thought you were dumb.
But your English is surprisingly good!
Hey! Why does that matter!
What do you want us to do?
Can you ever decide on what you want?
I guess not.
I don’t know how
That’s how I was raised.
Not just me...
Most of us grow up trapped
between your dreams and our own.
We're never allowed to speak our minds.
Then how do we know what you want?
Put in some effort.
Try to understand.
Don’t we kids
try to understand grown ups?
Then why can’t you do the same.
I get it now!
No matter what
I’ll marry Tanisha.
As if!
My daughter is out of your league.
Hey!
Why not?
He is family, too.
But he’s not our caste.
So what?
Oh!
You will pick matches
from our caste for your children.
But I should get my daughter
married to someone else.
I realized it a while ago
that it does not matter anymore.
Here on out,
my son makes his own decisions.
What else am I going to ask now?
I going to ask for Magic.
Then bring her here.
What?
This is some sort of trap, isn’t it?
I swear it isn’t.
Bring her here.
I'll bring her.
Bring her!
We insist!
I'll bring her for sure.
Do it already!
Okay! Thank you!
Son-in-law,
please don’t leave me!
Krishna!
Do you know where Magic is?
I know exactly where she’d be, Uncle.
Thank you! Thank you!
Co-in-law.
I'm sorry for what I did.
We’re all family now!
Water under the bridge.
Okay!
Hey, Bugger!
Didn’t you get married?
In this fast-paced world...
the only face
that brings me peace is yours.
I love you!
I love you too, my bugger.
♪ A little love is enough
To fill my soul ♪
♪ Here, our lives are made whole ♪
♪ A smile brimming with joy
Is enough ♪
♪ Every trace of pain drifts away ♪
♪ Hearts that speak
Become boundless love ♪
- Babu!
- Hey, Mangababu. Get over here!
I refuse!
Why does it have to me?
Oh, no!
♪ A yearning
To bring my heart's dreams to life ♪
♪ O Radiant One ♪
- I’m like that too.
- Is that right?
- Have some tea.
- Coffee!
Bless us!
We wish you the best.
- Let’s go to our new home.
- I'm leaving, Mom.
Don’t laugh!
It’s getting hard to shoot
with our star here.
Look at his fan club.
Many roses (Roja) welcomes
the only Roja (Name).
I yelled at him!
My Love...
I forgot the lines.
And if she doesn’t approve--
Line?
Hey, Magic!
What do I do with you?
Tell her
how much Magic means to you.
I’ll smack you down
Good Lord!
Why don’t you say “Cut!”?
Magic! Magic! Magic!
- Get Lost
- Oh, no!
We need to get rid of street dogs.
You’re doing "Naipavangal" instead
of "Parithabangal."
Yes, indeed.
“Naipavangal”, “Maadupavangal.”
That’s the only thing Gopi & Sudhagar
hasn’t done yet.
Only because
there are no audience for it.
He won’t let us show our acting ability.
Thinking it over and over--
Your line is “Magic.”
Next shot can be from the front.
Are you still reading that!?
I’m not coming up!
I’d rather take a photo with her.
What’s my line again?
Slow down, Director.
You’re enjoying this way too much.
First of all...
“Thaipusam”
I meant to say “Puratasi”.
Sorry! Sorry!
Beforehand, You need to woo Magic
and her Mom--
Not her Mom!
I got tongue tied.